{
    "subject": "resource/Flash_of_Genius_(film)",
    "predicate": "ontology/starring",
    "object": "resource/Greg_Kinnear",
    "human_readable": "The film 'Flash of Genius' stars Greg Kinnear.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8542072176933289,
            "question": "Has Greg Kinnear won any awards for his role in 'Flash of Genius'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8493896722793579,
            "question": "What is the name of the film starring Greg Kinnear?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8249673843383789,
            "question": "Who stars in the film 'Flash of Genius'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7468908429145813,
            "question": "Is Greg Kinnear an actor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7226242423057556,
            "question": "Who directed the film 'Flash of Genius'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5923335552215576,
            "question": "What is the plot of the film 'Flash of Genius'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5400651693344116,
            "question": "Is there a soundtrack for the film 'Flash of Genius'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4645993113517761,
            "question": "What genre is the film 'Flash of Genius' likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4422403573989868,
            "question": "What year was the film 'Flash of Genius' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3969925343990326,
            "question": "Are there any true stories depicted in the film 'Flash of Genius'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The film 'Flash of Genius' stars Greg Kinnear.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3889_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was the film 'Flash of Genius' released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3889_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film 'Flash of Genius' likely to be?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3889_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there a soundtrack for the film 'Flash of Genius'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3889_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3889_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3889_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3889_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3889_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3889_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3889_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3889_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3889_91.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3889_96.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3889_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, the answer is:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`\n\nThis is because all four documents mention that \"The film ... stars Greg Kinnear\" or similar phrases, which confirm that Greg Kinnear indeed starred in the film \"Flash of Genius\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that \"Flash of Genius\" stars Greg Kinnear as the protagonist, Dr. Robert Kearns, which supports the given query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}